

MARIO CURKOVIC

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

◆ CROATIA

◆ +385 99 500 36 36

• DETAILS •

Croatia +385 99 500 36 36 mario.curkovic89@gmail.com

> Date of birth 16/12/1989

Nationality Croatian

LINKS

Hiro Consulting d.o.o.

SKILLS

Effective Time Management

Communication Skills					
Communication					
Creativity					
Teamwork					
Leadership					
JavaScript					
Adaptability					
SQL					
Java					
Spring					
Jenkins					
HTML					
CSS					
Jasper					
Primefaces					
jQuery					
Angular					
Hibernate					

Git

PROFILE

Proactive, ambitious, and hard-working professional with over 5 years of experience in software

development.

Wide broad experience including working and leading self-organizing teams, direct on-site and

video-conference communication with customers, agreeing and negotiating to start from system

requirements to delivery deadlines.

Worked on a daily basis in Java EE, Angular, and Postgres SQL focusing on code re-usability, performance optimizations, and scalability.

Went through multiple cost/performance analyses, leading to some performance trade-offs to satisfy agreed deadlines.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Developer at Ericsson, Split

January 2014 — April 2018

- Worked with a team of expert coders to write maintainable code and maintain existing software to improve performance and fix bugs
- Oversaw a team of 13 engineers and technicians focused on streamlining and maintaining corporate projects (automated testing)
- Interfaced with clients in person or via videoconferencing to discuss project goals, aesthetics, and requirements
- Provided written and face-to-face feedback to developers
- Designed and wrote automated tests to ensure consistent production of the desired results Built modern test automation framework using Java, JUnit, Angular, and Selenium and supported the company's development and testing processes
- Designed and maintained CI/CD structure to allow constant automated test execution and software verification on different testing levels

Tech. stack: Java, Junit, TestNG, Git, Jira, CI/CD, Jenkins, Maven, Docker, HTML, CSS, Jasper, Selenium

Software Developer at Analyticom d.o.o., Split

May 2018 — April 2022

- Built modern applications using Java, Spring, PostgreSQL, Angular, and Primefaces and supported the company's development and testing processes
- Continually identified areas that needed improvement and guided junior developers in measuring the level of adjustment required
- Oversaw the creation of reports concerning software project specifications Worked with a team of expert coders to write maintainable code and maintain existing software to improve performance and fix bugs
- Consulted with clients to identify their projects' specifications and follow up with deployed applications' status and any technical issues

	K	ey	/C	lo	ć
-	_				-

Selenium

Docker

- Obtained, studied, and manipulated data to analyze systems' full capabilities
 Constantly suggested code and performance analysis, and optimizations and was involved in both short and long-term project planning
- Worked in agile teams (daily meetings, sprints, reviews, and retrospectives)
- Worked on projects with direct contact with clients (on-site meetings, video conferences)

Tech. stack: Java, Spring Boot, JUnit, Primefaces, JavaServer Faces, Git, Angular, Jira, Scrum, CI/CD, Bamboo, Jenkins, JFrog Artifactory, Maven, Keycloak, Docker, Oracle DB, Postgres DB, HTML, CSS, Hibernate, Jasper, Selenium

Software Developer at Hexagon Manufacturing Intelligence, Remote

May 2022

- Working on SimManager, Hexagon's web-based simulation process and data management application used for car development and testing (simulating incidents).
- Migrating to new technologies (Primefaces to Angular frontend), cleaning existing code, and optimizing the performance of existing and newly created processes.

Tech. stack: Java, Spring Boot, JUnit, Primefaces, JavaServer Faces, Git, Angular, Jira, CI/CD, Jenkins, Javascript, jQuery, Gradle

Software Developer at APIS IT d.o.o., Remote

October 2022 — January 2023

- Worked on the government system (customs department) for refactoring and improving the application to use the new currency in Croatia (Euro).
- Detected affected areas, analyzed dependent subsystems, optimized code, and performance, and added unit testing and instructions for manual tests.

Software Developer at Aya Yacht, Remote

February 2023 — May 2023

- Created and implemented Web Shop custom-tailored solution for the client
- Created backend and admin app to serve fully customizable frontend eCommerce template picked by client

Tech. stack: Bootstrap, Twig, axios, PHP, JavaScript, Web Design, Programming, Software Development, CSS, HTML, jQuery, Front-end Development

Web: aya-yacht.com

Software Developer at BazenShop, Remote

October 2022 — January 2023

- Created and implemented Web Shop custom-tailored solution for the client
- Created backend and admin app to serve fully customizable frontend eCommerce template picked by client

Tech. stack: Bootstrap, Twig, axios, PHP, JavaScript, Web Design, Programming, Software Development, CSS, HTML, jQuery, Front-end Development

Web: bazenshop.hr

EDUCATION

Master of Computer science, Faculty of Electrical Engineering, Mechanical Engineering and Naval Architecture in Split

September 2008 — September 2013

Master of Computer science, The University of L'Aquila, L'Aquila

February 2013 — June 2013

On student exchange program (ERASMUS) - Master thesis (Android mobile application)